{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_43","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567253726","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567253725"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 37dc5862-d997-4cfc-ae38-81b5e9b58ecd"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.show.82"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_w-f-ch"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567263323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567263323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 16aceb46-d344-42bb-9b5d-e7826b98572a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_k-g-ch"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567266469","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567266468"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 16aceb46-d344-42bb-9b5d-e7826b98572a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_t-b-ch"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567269567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567269567"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 16aceb46-d344-42bb-9b5d-e7826b98572a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_z-a-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567272783","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567272783"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 16aceb46-d344-42bb-9b5d-e7826b98572a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_y-ch-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567278129","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567278129"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 16aceb46-d344-42bb-9b5d-e7826b98572a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-ch-j"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567281711","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567281711"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 16aceb46-d344-42bb-9b5d-e7826b98572a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_t-ch-p"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567284567","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567284566"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 16aceb46-d344-42bb-9b5d-e7826b98572a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_ch-b-s"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567287831","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567287831"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 16aceb46-d344-42bb-9b5d-e7826b98572a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_j-z-ch"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567291088","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567291088"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 16aceb46-d344-42bb-9b5d-e7826b98572a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-ch-e"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567295005","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567295005"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 16aceb46-d344-42bb-9b5d-e7826b98572a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-g-ch"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567300804","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567300804"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 16aceb46-d344-42bb-9b5d-e7826b98572a"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_CH..CH.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.83"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_u-g-ch"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567309937","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567309937"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_8-7-15"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567315062","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567315062"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_14_8-9-14"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 14"," userResponse":" 14"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567320171","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567320171"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_14_8-4-14"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 14"," userResponse":" 14"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567339865","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567339864"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_2-10-3"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567349882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567349882"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-12-13"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 16"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567358947","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567358947"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-10-3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567368737","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567368737"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_16_16-10-3"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 16"," userResponse":" 16"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567373896","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567373896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_11-7-15"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567384093","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567384093"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_15_11-7-15"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 15"," userResponse":" 15"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567390177","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567390177"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-12-13"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567398486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567398486"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-12-13"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 12"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567405605","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567405605"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_11_11-12-13"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 11"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567416344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567416344"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_17_17-3-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 17"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567440709","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567440709"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_17_17-3-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 17"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567447167","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567447166"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_17_17-3-5"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 17"," userResponse":" 17"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567452214","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567452214"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-11"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 10"," userResponse":" 10"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567458756","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567458755"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 2e63c379-f470-41e9-b45e-3d7bf6d2d632"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF5-BL3.incr.10"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_10_1-10-11"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567469323","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567469323"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_a_a-f-n"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567476602","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567476602"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_b_t-n-b"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" b"," userResponse":" b"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567481284","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567481284"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_ch_d-s-ch"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ch"," userResponse":" ch"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567484532","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567484532"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_d_p-d-e"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" d"," userResponse":" d"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567488320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567488319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_e_w-y-e"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" e"," userResponse":" e"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567494400","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567494400"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_f_f-d-j"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" f"," userResponse":" f"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567497965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567497965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_g_z-i-g"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" g"," userResponse":" g"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567503786","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567503786"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_h_g-n-h"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" h"," userResponse":" h"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567510936","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567510936"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_i_i-ch-r"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" i"," userResponse":" i"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567514115","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567514115"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_j_j-h-t"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" j"," userResponse":" j"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567520126","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567520126"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_k_j-k-o"," problemNumber":" 11"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" k"," userResponse":" k"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567523683","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567523682"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_l_w-l-f"," problemNumber":" 12"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" l"," userResponse":" l"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567528485","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567528485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_m_m-n-s"," problemNumber":" 13"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" m"," userResponse":" m"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567534135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567534135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_n_b-h-n"," problemNumber":" 14"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" n"," userResponse":" n"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567537745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567537745"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_o_w-o-y"," problemNumber":" 15"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567541309","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567541309"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_p_m-p-s"," problemNumber":" 16"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" p"," userResponse":" p"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567549435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567549435"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_r_v-r-d"," problemNumber":" 17"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" r"," userResponse":" r"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567552712","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567552712"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_s_i-h-s"," problemNumber":" 18"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" s"," userResponse":" s"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567562211","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567562211"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_t_t-r-z"," problemNumber":" 19"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" t"," userResponse":" t"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567566745","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567566744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_u_u-i-h"," problemNumber":" 20"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" u"," userResponse":" u"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567572007","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567572007"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_v_v-i-k"," problemNumber":" 21"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" v"," userResponse":" v"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567575466","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567575466"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_w_d-w-m"," problemNumber":" 22"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" w"," userResponse":" w"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567579182","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567579181"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_y_n-y-f"," problemNumber":" 23"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" y"," userResponse":" y"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567588657","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567588656"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" z"," userResponse":" z"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 24"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548567594407","data":{"timestamp":" 1548567594406"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190127_083405"," gameId":" 77d40d63-c20f-42f6-a759-3b721205c534"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.lc_A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_3"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_z_z-j-h"," problemNumber":" 24"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}